<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
- Copyright 2018 Sune Vuorela <sune@vuorela.dk>
- SPDX-License-Identifier: MIT
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kookbook</id>
  <name>Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kookboek</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kokbok</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kookbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKookbookxx</name>
  <summary>Recipe manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor de receptes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestor de receptes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Správce receptů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Rezeptverwaltung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Recipe manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestor de recetas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de recettes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Pengelola resep</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestore delle ricette</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Beheerder van recepten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Matoppskriftsprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestor de receitas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de receitas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Správca receptov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik receptov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Recepthanterare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для керування рецептами</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxRecipe managerxx</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <developer_name>Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="id">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nn">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Sune Vuorela</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxSune Vuorelaxx</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>Kookbook is a simplistic recipe manager that will help you to maintain a collection of your favorite recipes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kookbook és un gestor simplista de receptes que ajuda a mantenir una col·lecció amb les receptes preferides.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Kookbook és un gestor simplista de receptes que ajuda a mantindre una col·lecció amb les receptes preferides.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Kookbook ist eine einfache Rezeptverwaltung für Ihre gesammelten Lieblingsrezepte.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kookbook is a simplistic recipe manager that will help you to maintain a collection of your favourite recipes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kookbook es un sencillo gestor de recetas que le ayudará a mantener una colección con sus recetas favoritas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kookbook est un gestionnaire de recette minimaliste pour vous aider à gérer une collection de vos recettes préférées.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Kookbook adalah pengelola resep sederhana yang akan membantu kamu memelihara koleksi resep favoritmu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kookbook è un gestore di ricette semplificato che ti aiuterà a mantenere una raccolta delle tue ricette preferite.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kookbook is een eenvoudige receptenbeheerder die u zal helpen om een verzameling van uw favoriete recepten te onderhouden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Kookbook er eit enkelt program for å halda oversikt over favoritt­oppskriftene dine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kookbook é um gestor de receitas simplista que o ajudará a manter uma colecção das suas receitas favoritas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Kookbook é um gerenciador de receitas simples que o ajudará a manter uma coleção de suas receitas favoritas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kookbook je poenostavljen upravljalnik receptov, ki vam bo pomagal ohranjati zbirko vaših najljubših receptov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kokbok är en naiv recepthanterare som hjälper till att hantera en samling favoritrecept.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kookbook — проста програма для керування записами рецептів, яка допоможе вам працювати зі збіркою ваших улюблених рецептів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKookbook is a simplistic recipe manager that will help you to maintain a collection of your favorite recipes.xx</p>
    <p>Recipes can be synced with others using external tools like git repositories, nextcloud or many other services.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Les receptes es poden sincronitzar amb altres usant eines externes com repositoris git, nextcloud o molts altres serveis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Les receptes es poden sincronitzar amb altres usant eines externes com repositoris git, nextcloud o molts altres serveis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Abgleich von Rezepten mit externen Diensten wie Git-Quelltextarchiven, Nextcloud und anderen ist möglich.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Recipes can be synced with others using external tools like git repositories, nextcloud or many other services.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Las recetas se pueden sincronizar usando herramientas externas, como repositorios git, nextcloud y otros servicios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Les recettes peuvent être synchronisées avec d'autres utilisant des outils externes, comme des dépôts « git », « Nextcloud » ou de nombreux autres services.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Resep bisa disinkronkan dengan yang lain menggunakan alat eksternal seperti git repositories, nextcloud atau banyak layanan lainnya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Le ricette possono essere sincronizzate con altri utilizzando strumenti esterni come repository git, nextcloud o molti altri servizi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Recepten kunnen gesynchroniseerd worden met andere door externe hulpmiddelen als git-opslagruimten, nextcloud of vele andere services te gebruiken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Du kan synkronisera oppskriftene med andre via eksterne verktøy, som Git-depot, Nextcloud og andre tenester.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">As receitas podem ser sincronizadas com outras pessoas, usando ferramentas externas como repositórios de Git, Nextcloud ou muitos outros serviços.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">As receitas podem ser sincronizadas com outros usando ferramentas externas como repositórios git, nextcloud ou muitos outros serviços.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Recepte lahko sinhronizirate z drugimi z zunanjimi orodji, kot so skladišča git, nextcloud ali številnih drugih storitve.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Recept kan synkroniseras med andra genom att använda externa verktyg som git-arkiv, nextcloud eller många andra tjänster.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Рецепти можна синхронізувати із іншими джерелами за допомогою зовнішніх інструментів, зокрема сховищ git, nextcloud або багатьох інших служб.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxRecipes can be synced with others using external tools like git repositories, nextcloud or many other services.xx</p>
  </description>
</component>
